( low , distant whooshing )
( whooshing grows louder , subsides )
( waves swelling )
( crashing loudly )
♪ ♪
( waves crashing in distance )
( waves continue crashing )
( quiet , shuddering breath )
( pills rattling quietly )
Adrian ?
( waves continue crashing )
( panting quietly )
- ( Adrian grunts ) - ( rustling )
( trembling breaths )
( waves continue crashing )
( glass clinks quietly )
( panting quietly )
( air humming )
( waves rumbling in distance )
( large wave crashes )
( waves continue crashing )
♪ ♪
( door clunks open )
( lights hum )
( electronics humming )
( gasps quietly )
Come on .
♪ ♪
( clangs loudly )
( shuddering )
( takes a deep breath )
♪ ♪
( panting )
( dog whines )
( Cecilia gasps )
( sighs )
Zeus , I 'm sorry .
I can 't take you with me .
I 'm sorry .
Shit . I 'm not gonna leave you with that thing on .
Okay .
Come here .
It 's okay . Good boy .
There you go .
( grunts , pants )
Come here .
- ( thump ) - ( car alarm blaring )
♪ ♪
( panting )
( grunts )
( grunts , pants )
♪ ♪
( panting )
Fuck .
Emily , where are you ?
( sighs )
Shit .
( distant birdcalls )
( branches creaking )
( panting )
( gasps excitedly )
Cecilia , what is going on ?
- Are you okay ? - ( lock clunks )
I 'll explain later .
Just go , Emily .
Go . ( screams , gasps )
Open the fucking door , Cecilia !
What is happening ?
Open the door !
- No . - ( Emily screaming ) - Open this door !
- Open the door ! - ( screaming )
- Open the fucking door ! - EMILY : I 'm going , I 'm going .
Cecilia , get back here !
EMILY : Jesus ! ( gasps )
Get back here now !
You can 't do this ! Get back here !
♪ ♪
Cee .
How long have you been up ?
A few hours .
Can 't sleep .
Now , you know , if you close your eyes
and you lie down , that usually helps .
( chuckles )
Um , don 't think being tired
gets you out of our little deal , now .
I swore to your sister I 'd get you to step outside my house .
Hey , Cee .
He 's not out there .
I promise .
( door creaking )
( birds singing )
♪ ♪
( muffled running footsteps )
( gasps quietly )
( panting )
I 'm sorry . I 'm just ...
- I 'm not ready yet . - Hey , it 's okay , Cee .
That 's the furthest you 've gone since you 've been here , okay ?
So , as far as I 'm concerned , you just walked on the moon .
( chuckles softly )
( " Kids " by Rich Brian playing )
♪ Hey , uh , I 'm putting numbers on the board ♪
♪ And blowing more digits ♪
JAMES : I can 't work with this goddamn thing .
♪ Shout out my parents ♪
♪ My mother gave birth to four winners ♪
♪ All of the players in the game ♪
♪ It 's always cold benches ♪
♪ Been in the studio ♪
♪ I forgot how to sleep ♪
♪ Not tryna make an album ♪
♪ They forget ' bout in a week ♪
♪ They said the fruit never goin ' fall far from the tree ♪
♪ I used to be the kid , now the kids wanna be me ♪
♪ Tripping ' bout my future ♪
♪ Like way before there was cameras ♪
♪ Hella plans on my calendar ... ♪
- ( doorbell rings ) - ( knocking )
It 's all right .
I got it .
( music stops )
Do I know you ?
- Do I owe you money ? - A lot .
A lot ? I told y 'all about running up on me in my house .
- ( door closes ) - Hey . Cee .
Tell her she can 't take you back .
We 're keeping you .
What are you doing here , Emily ?
Well , it 's nice to see you , too , sis .
JAMES : I 'm gonna go see what Sydney 's up to .
- Just ... - Mm .
Yeah .
This is not fair .
I asked you not to come over .
He knows where you live . He will follow you .
Yes , well , I have some news .
There is no news that justifies this .
Okay , I have a plan , and I just ...
I-I need you to-to go along with it
and just not be in control for one second .
I 'm not trying to control you , boo .
I 'm desperately trying to tell you that
you don 't need to cut me off anymore .
Because he 's dead .
What ?
♪ ♪
Hey .
What did he do to you ?
Can you talk to me ?
( sets phone on table )
♪ ♪
CECILIA : It just doesn 't make any sense .
He was ... he was in ... he was ...
in complete control of everything , you know ? Just ...
Including me .
He controlled how I looked and ...
what I wore and what I ate .
( chuckles )
And ...
then it was controlling when I left the house and
what I said .
And eventually ...
what I thought .
And if ...
if he didn 't like what he assumed I was thinking
h-he ... he would ...
JAMES : He 'd what ? He 'd ...
He would ... he would hit you ?
Amongst other things .
He wanted to have a baby .
And I knew that if we did that , that I ...
I would never be able to get away from him , so ...
I took birth control without him knowing it .
But , um , that can only go on for so long , so ...
I called you . ( chuckles softly )
Hey .
You 're here with us now .
And you 're safe .
He 's gone .
♪ ♪
I 'm not telling you to aim low .
I 'm just saying , e-explore more than one option , okay ?
Don 't limit your choices to just
one school in the whole country .
But that one school is my goal .
Parsons is my goal .
Yeah , I told you to have goals ... plural .
I think it 's important to have goals , James .
Uh , hey .
( continues clapping )
Look at you , getting out into the world .
You know , by next year , you 'll make it across the street .
( chuckles )
( James humming )
Uh , hey , Cee .
- Hmm ? - Something came for you .
No one knows I 'm here .
JAMES : So , who 's it from ?
♪ ♪
Thank you both for coming in .
As the appointed attorney
representing my late brother 's discretionary trust ,
I 'm required to enact his final wishes .
And he stipulated that I do this in person .
He wanted me to read a ... a prepared statement .
( papers rustling )
" Cecilia ,
" although our relationship was far from perfect ,
" I at least thought we had built up enough trust
" that you would talk to me
" rather than running away from what you
- perceived us to have . " - No , no . Sorry .
You 're not allowed to do that .
- I 'm required to read this . - She 's not required to listen .
E-mail me a copy , and we will read it .
You bet .
I 'm just trying to do my job .
Your job is to explain the money
- you mentioned on the phone . - I mentioned Cecilia
specifically is named in Adrian 's trust .
- That is why we 're sitting here . - Yes .
For the same reason so many women in Adrian 's life
got close to him : his money .
If there was a chance of physically being close to him ,
we would not be here for any amount of money .
You are physically close to him .
He 's in that urn over there .
And as per his final wishes , you 're getting $ 5 million ,
estate and income tax free .
Now , the money will be staggered
in installments of $ 100,000
each month for the next four years or so ,
contingent , of course , on the fine print .
You can 't commit a crime , et cetera .
Normally , I would have a 120-day contestability period ,
but I 'm gonna waive my rights in that regard .
So ...
as soon as I have your signature
and your banking information ,
I can start releasing the funds .
CECILIA : Okay , you can come in now .
( music playing quietly )
( Cecilia chuckling )
- Uh-oh . - Oh , hey .
- ( laughs ) - Wait , wait . Where you at ?
- Okay . - Okay .
- Can we look now ? - CECILIA : Careful .
Yes , you can look .
- Ta-da ! - Oh .
Wow . Thanks , Cee .
Wow , that 's nice . L-Look at that .
- A ladder ? - ( Cecilia laughs )
JAMES : Excuse you ?
I know I didn 't hear you just say that .
- I meant to say thank you . - What do you say ? Uh-huh .
You 're welcome . Well , I-I knew you needed a new one ,
and that one just ... that has to go .
That 's so nice of you , Cee . Thank you so much .
That 's very sweet of you . Thank you .
I just ... I wanted to thank you for ,
you know , letting me stay here
and for taking such good care of me , so ...
And Sydney can also use ladders .
Don 't think I 'm helping you paint .
I wouldn 't even bother to ask you .
No , not for , like , painting , obviously ,
but just for a lot of things .
You climb them to get things like-like stuff like that .
That 's so strange . God , I wish you had , like ...
Oh , wait , you could totally
- use the ladder . - A ladder to climb up ...
Yeah , the ladder 's cool .
- Okay . - This happened to just pop up there by itself ?
- It happened to just be here , so ... - Mm-hmm .
- CECILIA : ... it 's convenient . - Wow .
What is it ?
- It has my name on it . - That 's weird .
- And it looks like your handwriting . - I don 't know ...
- You sure it 's weird ? - I just got a ladder , so ...
- If you think it 's weird . - I don 't know what ...
- Yeah , yeah , yeah . - Let 's see .
- A cool ladder is all . - ( inhales sharply )
It 's a new bank account , um , with your name on it ,
and I 'm gonna put $ 10,000 in it every month
for the rest of the year .
I called the account " Parsons . "
( chuckling )
You 're going to fashion school , kid .
Hey , whoa , Cee , Cee , that 's ... that 's too much , Cee .
Come on , are you sure you can do that ?
Let me put it this way .
( chuckling ) : She can probably go to grad school , too .
( singsongy ) : I 'm going to Parsons .
JAMES ( laughing ) : She can go to Parsons .
CECILIA : You 're going to Parsons .
- ( laughing ) - Oh , my God .
Oh , wait , no .
We got to cel ... we got to celebrate .
And I don 't want TV dinners , microwave nothing , we ...
Oh , it 's , like , I guess too bad
we don 't have anything at all to celebrate with .
- Hey ... ! - Whoo-whoo !
- ( laughter ) - JAMES : I don 't know why you dancing .
You can 't have none , ' cause you 're not 21 .
- Yes , I can . - CECILIA : Oh , come on .
Just , like , a little bit .
He said the other day that I was mature for my age .
- That 's right . - He did .
- A mature child . - I heard you say that .
- I remember . - Hey , hold up , hold up , hold up .
This ain 't fair , okay ? Two against one .
I 'm just an innocent man trying to do right .
Are you scared ? Are you scared ?
This a ... this is abuse . I 'm a cop .
- Are you-you scared ? - You realize I 'm a cop .
- I got him , I got him . - Hey , hey , hey .
- ( Sydney hooting ) - ( James grunting )
- I got him , Sydney ! I got him ! - SYDNEY : No , he 's got me !
- ( Sydney whimpers ) - ( James grunting )
- Oh ! I 'll protect you ! - ( Sydney squeals )
( rummaging )
( paper rustling )
( soft , rapid clicking )
( takes deep breath )
( soft clicking continues )
- ( clicking stops ) - ( trembling breaths )
( sighs )
( sizzling )
Morning .
You want some breakfast ?
Nah , nah , I got to go .
You know , I 'm a little hungover , believe it or not .
Ugh . Me , too .
Champagne does that to me every time .
- We 're getting old , Cee . - ( laughs )
We old . ( chuckles )
These winter mornings are killing me .
All right , look , I 'm out of here .
Um , I 'll be back around 7 : 00 .
- Okay . - All right ?
- Oh , uh , Cee . - Hmm ?
You mind getting Sydney up ?
She 's actually pretty excited , thanks to you .
She , uh ... she might need a little help staying focused .
( chuckles ) You got it .
( footsteps departing )
( door opens )
( door closes )
Syd , come on , girl .
You 're gonna be late .
( sizzling continues )
( sizzling intensifies )
CECILIA : Shit !
Shit , shit .
- Shit . ( groans ) - SYDNEY : No , no , no , no , no .
No , don 't use water . No .
Excuse me . Sorry .
( hissing )
( Cecilia sighs )
- Oh . - Wow .
( laughs )
You did that .
Yeah .
You think we can salvage it ?
- ( laughs ) No . - No ?
No . Sorry .
( dog barking in distance )
( wind whistling )
- ( door creaks opens ) - ( dog barks in distance )
( door closes )
( footsteps )
( rapid typing nearby )
( soft , rapid clicking )
( low , deep growling )
( inhales deeply )
( low growling continues )
James ?
( floorboard creaking )
♪ ♪
( trembling breaths )
( floorboards creaking )
( distant footsteps )
( shuddering breaths )
♪ ♪
( rustling in distance )
( floorboards creaking )
♪ ♪
( clicking )
( door creaks opens )
( soft , rapid clicking )
( gasps quietly )
( shuddering breaths )
( crickets chirping )
( shuddering )
( leaves rustling in wind )
( wind whistling )
( sighs )
( breathing heavily )
( low breathing )
( creaking )
( soft , rapid clicking )
( door creaks )
( locks clunk )
( floorboard creaking )
( blanket drops to floor )
( breathing heavily )
( gasps )
( panting )
( brief , soft clicking )
( soft , rapid clicking )
( creaking )
♪ ♪
( breathing deeply )
( soft thump )
( brief , soft clicking )
( soft , rapid clicking )
- ( gasps ) James ! - ( clattering )
James ! James , James !
Yeah , yeah , what ?
What-what happened ? What happened ? What ?
I saw something right there . They were right there .
There were footprints . I saw it .
You-you saw ... you saw footprints ?
I saw ... I ... Yes , I saw ... On the sheets .
I saw it right there .
- I saw them . - On the sheet ?
( panting ) : I saw it .
There was someone in here . There was someone in here .
Syd , put that stupid thing away .
Y-You 're the one who bought it for me .
Who you gonna spray ? Who ?
James , I saw it .
I swear .
Hey , Cee .
Adrian will haunt you if you let him .
Don 't let him .
Now , you should try and get some sleep .
You have an important job interview tomorrow ,
and I don 't want the memory of this motherfu
that ...
this person to ruin it .
- Okay ? - Okay , yeah .
- Sorry . - Yeah .
( breathing deeply )
CECILIA : After Cal Poly , I worked in Paris
for six months .
That was the best time of my life , for sure .
Except for this next phase , of course .
( chuckles ) Take a seat .
So , any reason you worked in Paris in particular ?
Is that where all the beautiful women in the world
have to go as a rule ?
Well , I speak a little ... a little French ,
and I 've always wanted to live there .
So , after I graduated ,
I went out there on a totally student budget .
I slept in a broom closet , literally .
I started this firm in a supply closet , literally .
( chuckling ) : There you go .
- So we both know the value of closet space . - Yeah .
Let me see some of your work .
Yes , of course .
( clears throat )
( unzipping )
Uh , um ...
( chuckles )
I don 't ... Uh , I know that I ...
I know I put them in here , so I ... so I apologize .
I don 't know what happened .
- Um ... - It 's okay .
Uh , you can send it to us whenever you get a chance .
Okay .
Uh , so , uh , l-let me tell you about us .
Uh , at Ruler , we approach architecture on a human level .
First and ...
Are you okay ?
( inhales sharply )
Um , I 'm sorry .
Uh , I 'm just not feeling , um ...
Uh , would you like some water or ...
( inhales deeply )
( echoing ) : Cecilia ?
( amplified footsteps )
Are you feeling okay ?
( amplified thud )
( siren blaring )
( low chatter )
Cecilia .
Okay , so , uh , you probably shouldn 't drive
or operate any heavy machinery for the next few days ,
but other than that , you seem fine .
Either myself or my admitting will , uh , follow up with you
with the results of the blood test .
Okay ? Uh , can you just leave a number with the nurse ?
You guys can go home .
Okay .
You ready ?
Yeah .
( shower running )
( phone ringing in other room )
( phone continues ringing )
Hello ?
DR. LEE : Is Cecilia Kass there ?
That 's me .
Hi . Uh , this is Dr. Lee at St. Vincent 's .
So , we got the results of your blood test back ,
and it looks like the diazepam
was the most likely cause of you fainting .
Um , sorry , what diazepam ?
Well , your blood work showed a very high amount of it .
That would definitely explain what happened to you .
There 's something else I wanted to talk to you about ,
but I 'm not sure if we should do it over the phone , so , um ...
CECILIA : Tell him to stop .
TOM : Tell who to stop what ?
Tell him to stop what he 's doing .
Do you know what she 's babbling about ?
Nah , she hasn 't explained to me why we 're here yet ,
but being her very good friend , I know it 's a good reason ,
so I 'm gonna need you to sit up and listen .
Show a little respect .
One night , I was sitting ,
and I was thinking about how to leave Adrian .
I was planning the whole thing in my mind .
And he was staring at me ,
studying me .
And without me saying a single word ,
he said that I could never leave him .
That wherever I went ,
he would find me .
That he would walk right up to me
and I wouldn 't be able to see him ,
but that he would leave me a sign
so that I 'd know he was there .
The night I left him , I drugged him with that .
I lost the bottle that night .
And somehow , it found its way back to me .
So , what exactly are you saying ?
You lost the bottle , you found the bottle .
He 's not dead , Tom .
I have a pile of ashes in the box
that would disagree with you , Cecilia .
I don 't know how he 's done it .
He 's figured it out , though .
He has figured out a way to be invisible .
He is a world leader in the field of optics .
I-I ... I know that he could do this .
Something tells me you know exactly what I 'm talking about .
He 's not dead .
I just can 't see him .
Please tell him to stop .
Okay .
No , I agree with you .
Adrian was brilliant .
But it wasn 't because of anything he invented .
It was how he got in people 's heads .
That was his true genius ... knowing people 's weaknesses .
You think about it .
He came up with the perfect way to torture you even in death .
Only thing more brilliant
than inventing something that makes you invisible
is not inventing it but making you think he did .
My brother controlled me
long before he met you , Cecilia .
I hated him .
You and I , we got that in common .
( chuckles ) I was relieved
when I heard that he was dead .
He 's gone , Cecilia .
I saw his body .
Listen to me .
Don 't let him win by bringing him back to life .
♪ ♪
Hey .
Emily , I need to talk to you .
Well , at least now we have clarity .
Now I know what you really think of me .
- What ? - Thanks so much
for carving out the time to let me know how ...
quote , unquote ... " suffocating " I am to you .
What ? What are you ...
Not that I should have to say this ,
but I never expected any of that money .
( scoffs )
Emily , I-I don 't ... I don 't know what you 're talking about .
The e-mail ... the e-mail you sent me this morning .
- What e-mail ? - If that 's how you feel about me ,
don 't ask me to bail you out of your personal life anymore .
If you 're too stupid to know who the good guys are
and too weak to get away from the bad ones ,
don 't sob to me for charity .
I 'm out .
I didn 't send you the fucking e-mail .
I didn 't .
Someone is-is-is doing this to me .
He 's-he 's doing this to me .
Who 's ...
Adrian ?
Adrian sent me the e-mail . Okay .
You need some medication . Adrian is dead .
- Em , please , no . - ( lock clicks )
♪ ♪
( door creaks open )
( typing )
♪ ♪
( sniffles )
( crying )
( Cecilia sniffles )
Cee ?
( Cecilia sniffling )
It 's okay , Syd .
You-you know what I think we need ?
Um ...
I think we could kick Dad out and ...
( Sydney chuckles )
... have a little girls ' night .
Eat some cake . ( chuckles )
( laughs )
( sniffles )
Yeah .
I do like cake .
- ( smack , thud ) - ( Sydney grunts , whimpers )
Oh , my God . Sydney , are you okay ?
Why would you just ... Stop ! Stop ! Dad !
- What ? No . No , Sydney , I didn 't ... - Dad ! Dad .
- JAMES : What ? What-what ... - No , I ... - Dad , she ...
- What happened ? What happened ? - She-she hit me .
- JAMES : What ? - No . No , no , no .
James , I did not do that .
Sydney , I would never hit you . I love you .
I would never do that , James .
It was him . He 's here , I swear to you .
Enough . Enough .
Cee , enough .
Just stop it . Are you okay , baby ?
- I don 't want to stay here . - You-you all right ?
Sydney , I 'm sorry . I would never ...
Hey , hey . Cee .
Right now my priority is getting my baby somewhere safe .
Do you understand ?
Come on , baby . It 's okay .
CECILIA : No . James , please .
This is what he wants .
This is what he used to do when we were together .
He wants you to think that I did it .
This is what he does . He tries to isolate me ,
- and he tries to get me alone . - Hey !
You need to calm down .
You are scaring my daughter .
Now , if I were you , I would go to your sister 's place .
You don 't need to be here right now .
Come on , Sydney .
Sydney , Sydney , I 'm sorry . Sydney .
( takes a deep breath )
Where are you ?
Come on !
♪ ♪
Where are you ? Come on out .
Don 't hit a little girl .
Hit me !
♪ ♪
( crickets chirping )
So , why me , Adrian ?
You could have any woman you wanted . ( chuckles )
That 's the sad reality .
Right ?
And that 's what money and power buy you .
People .
So ...
why me ?
I 'm just a suburban girl who ...
stumbled into your life one night at a party .
( laughs )
Can 't you just forget I ever existed ?
There 's nothing left
for you to take .
( chuckles )
You 've already taken it all .
( Cecilia breathing shakily )
( sniffles )
( buttons beeping )
( line ringing )
( cell phone vibrating in distance )
( vibrating continues )
ADRIAN ( recorded ) : This is Adrian Griffin .
Please leave a message ,
and I 'll get back to you when I can .
( trembling breaths )
( Cecilia panting quietly )
( panting )
( buttons beeping )
( line ringing )
( vibrating loudly )
- ( phone beeps ) - ( vibrating stops )
♪ ♪
( sets phone down )
( sets knife down )
( soft , rapid clicking )
( trembling breaths )
( cell phone vibrating )
( rattling nearby )
( trembling breaths )
( wood creaking )
( soft , rapid clicking )
( creaking )
- ( gasps ) - ( paint can drops to floor )
- ( panting ) - ( clattering )
( footsteps running away )
♪ ♪
( creaking )
( grunting )
( panting )
( trembling breaths )
( gasps )
( faucet squeaks on )
( water running )
( trembling breaths )
( water continues running )
( faucet squeaks )
♪ ♪
( gagging )
( strained gasping )
( knife clatters on floor )
( grunts )
No ! ( yells , grunts )
- ( grunts ) - ( thump )
( panting )
( yells )
( soft , rapid clicking )
( breathing shakily )
( whimpers , groans )
( grunting )
( yells )
( panting )
( strained grunting )
- ( dish clangs ) - ( rapid clicking )
( grunts )
( panting )
( crickets chirping )
♪ ♪
- Cecilia ? - Yes . Go .
Please , hurry . Lock the doors .
- Lock the doors ! - You okay ?
Yes . Please , please just go .
Okay .
Just please hurry , please .
Stinson Beach ... that 's a long way from here .
♪ ♪
CECILIA : I-I just need to get something .
Do you mind waiting for me ?
I might be two minutes ,
I might be 20 , I don 't know , but ...
You could run me back to the city after .
- Sure . - Okay .
No problem .
( lock clunks )
( quiet , trembling breaths )
( clattering nearby )
- Zeus . - ( whining )
Hi . Hi .
( door clunks open )
( Zeus whines , whimpers )
( device chimes )
( buttons beeping )
( sighs )
12-14 ... 17 .
The day we met .
( device chimes , door whooshes open )
So romantic .
( soft , rapid clicking )
( clicking stops )
- ( machine clanks , whirs ) - ( gasps )
( soft whirring , rapid clicking )
( breathing heavily )
( rapid clicking )
( Zeus barking )
( panting )
( wave crashing )
( creaks quietly )
( soft , rapid clicking )
( waves crashing )
( trembling breaths )
( shuddering breaths )
( barking )
♪ ♪
Please , meet me tonight , if you can ,
in a pu ... in a public place .
( sniffles ) 8 : 00 at Yulan .
And if you can 't , I understand , but you have to tell me ,
because I have to call someone else ,
because I don 't think I have much time left .
Thank you . Thank you .
( sighs )
♪ ♪
( upbeat music playing inside )
( lively chatter )
( laughter )
♪ ♪
Hi .
Hey .
WAITER : Hey , guys . Welcome to Yulan .
My name is Taylor , and I will be
taking care of you this evening .
Do you know how this place works ?
I 'm assuming you order food , then you eat it .
Hmm , pretty much .
We just do things a little bit differently .
It 's all family style .
We 've been here before . It 's all good .
TAYLOR : Okay . Can I get you started with some water ?
- We have still or sparkling . - Just the free kind .
- ( chuckling ) : Okay , tap it is . - Cool .
Thank you for being here .
I love you .
You 're like a cop , Emily ,
and y-you have this brute-force strength
that is so , so comforting when I 'm in trouble ,
and it is really intimidating when I 'm not .
I mean , James actually is a six-foot cop ,
and he 's , I think , really intimidated by you .
As he should be .
I 'd kick his ass .
( laughing )
I would .
( chuckles ) You would .
( Cecilia takes a deep breath )
I need that strength in my life right now .
And I need you to believe what I 'm about to tell you .
Okay . I ...
Thank you , Taylor .
TAYLOR : All right . Uh , do you guys need more time
- with the drink menu ? - Yes .
Lots more time .
TAYLOR ( chuckling ) : Okay , no problem at all .
Emily .
I went to his house today .
- You went to Adrian 's house ? - Yes .
I just walked right in .
I found something that can prove what I 'm experiencing .
That can prove that Adrian is stalking me .
What is it ?
It 's some kind of suit that Adrian has built .
And it has cameras , and it somehow ...
What ?
( gasps , shudders )
( screaming )
( patrons murmuring )
♪ ♪
( Cecilia shuddering )
CECILIA : No , please . No !
You can 't do this . You can 't do this .
He killed her . He killed her .
Please , I didn 't do it !
I didn 't do it .
No ! No !
He killed her !
He did it ! You have to listen to me .
- Please , please , no . - DOCTOR : Try to relax .
Please , no !
( sobbing ) : No !
Listen to me ! No !
You motherfucker !
You killed her !
I see you ! I see you !
He 's here !
He 's here . He 's right here .
He 's right here . Please !
You can 't see him . He 's in the room .
You have to listen to me .
( crying ) : He 's right there . He 's gonna hurt me .
- Please . No ... - DOCTOR : Okay .
( softly ) : He 's right there .
- He 's here . - Okay .
He 's right ...
DOCTOR : There .
- Everything 's better now . - ( softly ) : He 's right there .
DOCTOR : Okay ? You 'll be all right .
( panting softly )
( footsteps )
ADRIAN : Surprise .
♪ ♪
DETECTIVE RECKLEY : Cecilia .
Can you confirm the person in this video is you ?
And can you confirm
you recently fainted during a job interview
due to a high amount of diazepam in your system ?
- I was drugged . - RECKLEY : Uh-huh .
You also sent your sister an e-mail a few days ago
saying you wished she was dead , didn 't you ?
( whispers ) : I have something .
I have something that will prove he 's alive .
I found it .
What do you have ?
I can 't tell you right now .
He 's listening .
He 's in the room , James .
You 're saying that the person who killed your sister
is in the room right now but we can 't see him ?
( quietly ) : Okay .
- Yeah . - Thank you .
- James . - ( door opens )
( door closes )
Tell me you don 't think I did this .
Tell me you know that .
( buzzer sounds in distance )
( door clanks shut )
I may as well have done it , though .
I brought Adrian into her life .
I did that .
I shouldn 't have walked out on you and left you alone .
I failed you .
NURSE : Is this bed giving you any problems , Cecilia ?
No .
Is there anything in the room that is distressing to you ?
Okay . Good .
I wanted to talk to you about something .
We checked the blood test
that you had done at the hospital last week .
Do you remember taking those blood tests ?
Yes .
Okay .
Well , did you know that you were pregnant ?
No .
Didn 't the doctor who took the test tell you ?
No , that can 't be right .
That 's ... that 's not true .
The test shows us that it was pretty recent .
We can 't be sure of exactly when ,
but it must have been sometime in the last month .
Sweetie , is there anyone we can call ?
Family ?
( voice fading ) : Any friends ?
Okay .
( continues indistinctly )
♪ ♪
( footsteps approaching )
TOM : It 's upsetting to see you in this condition .
Even though things ended badly for you and Adrian ,
I still look at you as family .
Are you my lawyer now ?
I 'm the lawyer for your source of income .
I represent my brother 's trust .
The money from his trust was payable to you
conditional upon you being subject
to criminal charges of any kind
or being ruled to be mentally incompetent .
Now , in light of your current situation ,
it 's my duty to inform you
that any further payments are to be halted .
I know that you set up a bank account
for a friend of yours to go to college ,
so I take no pleasure in relaying that .
I used to feel sorry for you .
The blood relative of a narcissist sociopath .
Permanent punching bag .
Handcuffed to his wallet .
But now ...
I can see you for what you really are .
You 're just the jellyfish version of him .
Everything but the spine .
I mean , you can try to litigate it ,
but that 's going to be an expensive option .
I can 't see it working .
( briefcase clasps clicking open )
However
if you sign this document and forfeit
your share of the trust ,
it 'll be a lot cleaner .
( whispering ) : Or there 's one option
where this all goes away .
Agree to have the baby
and go back to him .
You really think he didn 't know
you were secretly using birth control ?
Of course he did .
You should have known he 'd find out .
You knew him as well as I did .
He replaced them with something else .
You only thought you were taking birth control pills .
He was always going to find you no matter what he had to do .
He needs you because you don 't need him .
No one 's ever left him before .
But he 's punished you enough now .
Now that he knows you 're the mother of his child .
It 's time to stop playing games .
A new life with him can be given to you
with one phone call .
A life just like your old one with Adrian .
Cecilia , you don 't really have the choice right now .
Right now you 're a murderer .
But I can change that .
Adrian killed my sister ,
and you helped him .
I don 't expect you to make a decision right now .
I can come back in three days .
Be good to yourself until then .
We 'll be watching .
( newscast playing indistinctly )
REPORTER : Grab your umbrella .
Grab your rain jacket . Grab your rain boots .
You 're gonna need it .
You 'll need them for a couple days .
This pattern we 're in stays put .
We 've got this atmospheric river
pointed right here at central California .
And that means we 're gonna keep it cloudy and rainy
as we get through the rest of the week .
This is a lot of moisture coming in .
It 's going to mean heavy rainfall
and flash flooding concerns
right as we get to the end of the week .
It 's not until the weekend that we get our next chance
of seeing some dry conditions .
In fact , the next glimpse of sunshine even
doesn 't come until Sunday afternoon
when temperatures hit the mid-60s .
But until then , it 's going to be cool ,
it 's going to be damp , it 's going to be ...
♪ ♪
Open your mouth .
Tongue up .
Tongue down .
Okay . Good night .
( door creaks closed )
( lock clicks )
( creaking )
You won 't get the baby .
And you won 't get me .
( squishing thud )
( whimpers )
( thump )
( gasps ) There you are .
( suit crackling )
( grunts )
Fuck you !
( Cecilia groaning )
Get back in bed . Now .
( crackling )
( groaning )
♪ ♪
( grunts )
GUARD : Hey !
No ! No !
Please , no !
No !
Stop . Stop .
No , please . No .
No , stop ! No , stop .
He 's right there .
( grunts )
( crackling )
( running footsteps )
( low , deep growling )
( grunts )
( groans , grunts )
Lay down .
CECILIA : He 's right there .
He 's right behind you .
- Listen to me . - Who is ?
- Turn around . - I understand , Cecilia .
- He 's right there . - Lay down .
Listen to me !
- He 's right behind you . - Stay down .
( brief , rapid clicking )
- ( grunts ) - ( gun fires )
( screams )
( low , deep growling )
( panting )
( low growl )
( whimpers , mutters softly )
- ADRIAN : Bang . - ( whimpering , panting )
( guard crying softly )
- ( guard cries out ) - ( body thuds )
- ( panting ) - ( door creaks open )
( crackling )
( door creaks closed )
( door opens , closes )
( door closes )
( door opens )
- Get back ! - Hey ! Hey , whoa . - Okay .
Get back !
( alarm beeping )
( panting )
( clattering )
GUARD : She 's over here !
She 's over there ! Go right !
( grunting sigh )
( pants )
( thunder rumbling )
( panting quietly )
( choking )
ADRIAN : You think you 're learning how to beat me ,
so I 'm gonna truly teach you something .
If you fight me , I won 't ever hurt you .
I 'll find someone you love and hurt them instead .
( indistinct radio transmission )
Now you 've only got yourself to blame
for that innocent young girl 's death .
No , please .
Not Sydney . Adrian , no .
Hold it !
Show me your hands !
( grunts )
( low growling )
( crackling )
( grunts )
( groans )
( low growling )
( distant thunder rumbles )
GUARD : Hey !
Cecilia , don 't do anything stupid .
GUARD : I 'm over here !
Hey , stop her !
Heading towards the main exit !
♪ ♪
( engine starting )
( engine revving )
( horn honks )
( gasps )
What the ... What the fuck ?
WOMAN ( over phone ) : Hello ? Hello ?
Hey !
WOMAN : Harry , what 's going on ?
Harry .
Hey !
WOMAN : Hello ?
Harry , are you okay ?
- He 's fine . He 's fine . - What ?
- I promise . - Who ... who is this ?
( phone line ringing )
♪ ♪
JAMES ( over phone ) : This is James Lanier .
James , it 's me .
JAMES : Cee ? What ... How ...
- How are you calling ? - It doesn 't matter about that .
- You have to listen to me . - No , no , it-it does matter .
- Listen ... - Come on ! - ( horn honks )
You can 't be calling me .
- James , listen to me ! - Look , I ...
Sydney 's life is in danger .
Where are you right now ?
I 'm at work . She 's at the house .
( tires squeal )
Okay , you need to go to her right now , James .
Do you hear me ?
' Cause I 'm afraid Adrian is gonna do something to her .
( creaks quietly )
( footsteps thumping quietly )
( footsteps continue )
( door creaks quietly )
( quiet footsteps )
( gasps )
( trembling breaths )
( footsteps )
- ( squeals , whimpers ) - ( Adrian coughs )
( thudding )
( screaming )
( screaming continues )
- ( thump ) - ( gasps )
♪ ♪
( tires screech )
( gun clicks )
( keys jingle , lock clicks )
Sydney .
( gasping , choking )
- ( panting ) - Syd , you okay ?
- Sydney , Syd ... - ( thump )
( Sydney screams )
( grunting )
- ( grunts ) - ( Sydney screams )
- ( thumping ) - ( groans )
( grunts )
- ( thump ) - ( grunts )
Stop !
- ( thump ) - SYDNEY : No !
- ( screaming ) - ( James groaning )
Stop !
- ( Sydney screaming ) - ( grunting weakly )
( sobbing ) : Stop .
( thump )
Dad ! Dad !
No !
( Sydney crying )
( running footsteps )
Sydney , get down !
- ( crackling ) - ( shuddering breaths )
( crackling )
( crackling quietly )
( Sydney crying )
( James groaning )
- Don 't cry . - ( sniffling )
Tom ?
( gasps , shudders )
♪ ♪
ADRIAN ( muffled ) : Is someone there ?
Help . Help .
Please .
- Help ! - Stand clear !
( Adrian panting )
Police ! Show me your hands .
JAMES : Our tactical team
found Adrian this morning
tied up in his basement .
Looks like he was a victim of his brother
just like you were .
No .
No , James .
That 's not right .
Adrian did this to me .
He is not the victim here .
He was tied up in his basement .
If he faked his own death ,
he could fake his own kidnapping .
We have Tom 's body laying in my living room ,
wearing some sort of suit that you shot to pieces .
If it did work , it doesn 't now .
But-but we have a whole bunch of corroborative witnesses
from the psychiatric hospital
when it comes to seeing something strange .
Look , this is your best-case scenario
for getting your freedom back , okay ?
No .
I mean ...
I know Tom 's body is in your living room .
Yeah .
Adrian did everything before that , though .
He set his own brother up .
I know how this works , Cee .
I know . You don 't understand .
No , you don 't understand .
This is what he does .
He makes me feel like I 'm the crazy one .
This is ...
This is what he does .
And he 's doing it again .
Okay , okay , but listen .
I need you to keep that to yourself
- and let me do my job . - ( Cecilia sighs )
Okay ?
Just let me help you .
Yeah , but as long as Adrian 's around , you can 't help me .
( quiet , shuddering breaths )
( line ringing )
ADRIAN ( over phone ) : Cecilia ?
( sighs ) I 'm so glad you called .
♪ ♪
( wind whistling )
Well ... ( chuckles )
You look amazing .
I mean , you-you 've always ... you always look amazing .
I don 't feel amazing .
It 's all a lie .
Please , come on in .
It 's cold . Come on .
( Adrian clears throat )
So , I-I wanted to get us some simple takeout , but , of course ,
I-I started obsessing over what you 'd be in the mood for .
Hence , we have the OCD buffet of sushi , steak and pasta .
Or you might not be hungry at all .
Uh ... which is so logical
that it suddenly makes this feast look moronic .
CECILIA : I 'll have steak .
That 's a good choice .
( no audio )
( chuckles , clears throat )
My hand 's shaking . ( chuckles )
Uh ... ( clears throat )
( takes deep breath )
You know , you 're the only person in the world
who gets to see my hand shake .
It 's ' cause I need you , Cecilia .
I know I didn 't treat you the way
you should have been treated when we were together .
But I 've learned my lesson .
I would burn everything I own just to prove that to you .
Okay .
If you want to be a part of this child 's life
it has to start with honesty .
Of course .
Which means I need you to admit everything that you did .
That it was you ,
not your brother .
You .
( shuddering chuckle )
Cecilia .
I loved my brother .
And I thought he loved me , too .
I know it didn 't seem like it to the outside world , but ...
Tom controlled me .
( trembling ) : Just tell me the truth .
I need to know that I 'm not crazy , okay ?
And we can 't start this with a lie .
But I 'm not starting with a lie .
It wasn 't me .
I swear it .
Why can 't you just tell me the truth ?
I am .
Adrian , stop .
I need you to do this for me .
( over headphones ) : More than that ,
do it for you , Adrian .
ADRIAN : I 'm giving you exactly
what you 're asking for , Cecilia .
I am telling you the truth .
- Oh . - ( Cecilia crying )
Oh , no , no , no .
I know that you feel like you 're going insane sometimes .
But I 'm the only one who can help you .
Remember ?
Because I know you better than anyone else in the world .
I mean ... ( chuckles )
that shouldn 't come as a ...
surprise .
( chuckles softly , shudders )
I should go clean myself up .
( chuckles ) Of course .
( waves rumbling in distance )
( taking deep breaths )
( insects trilling )
( sighs )
( rapid fluttering )
- ( table rattling ) - ( grunting )
( no audio )
( grunts )
( gasping weakly )
( screams )
No ! No , no .
( sobbing , over headphones ) : No , no . What did you do ?
OPERATOR : 9-1-1 , what is your emergency ?
Please , please , you have to help me , please .
I 'm with somebody , and I think he 's ...
he 's tried to kill himself .
Hurry . You have to help .
You have to hurry . Please .
It 's , uh , 3333 Celestial Drive .
( no audio )
Please . ( sobbing )
( groaning weakly )
Surprise .
( wheezes )
( exhales slowly )
( no audio )
( running footsteps )
JAMES : Hey , hey .
- Hey . You okay ? - It 's okay .
- You okay ? What ... - I 'm okay . I 'm okay .
James , look at me . I 'm okay .
He killed himself .
He cut his own throat .
There 's security camera video of it .
( soft , rapid clicking )
You never did want to get him
admitting anything on tape , did you ?
Of course I did .
I just didn 't know he was that unstable .
You heard it , right ?
James ?
What 'd it sound like to you ?
It sounded a lot like he killed himself .
♪ ♪
( music fades )